<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Siobhán Keating, Technical Writer</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Siobhán Keating, Technical Writer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is docs-as-code?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs-as-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs-as-code/</guid>
      <description>What is a docs-as-code workflow? A docs-as-code workflow means applying software development processes and tools to technical documentation. As a Technical Writer (TW), you write content in plain text format using a code editor, rather than a markup language like XML and a content management system. You publish docs using a static site generator rather than a complex publishing system. TWs work with docs as developers work with code, relying on a source control system to track changes in the documentation suite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siobhán Keating - Technical Writer</title>
      <link>http://example.org/siobhan-keating-technical-writer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 15:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/siobhan-keating-technical-writer/</guid>
      <description>I am a technical writer I love to write and I feel my writing helps people understand technology and apply knowledge in their use of an application or system. I have 20 year&amp;rsquo;s experience working in the IT sector. I include here some generic examples of my writing, to demonstrate what technical writing means to me and to describe my experience of the docs-as-code workflow.
 What is a Technical Writer Best practices for technical documentation What is docs-as-code?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a Technical Writer?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/what-is-a-technical-writer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 15:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/what-is-a-technical-writer/</guid>
      <description>##What is a Technical Writer?##
A Technical Writer (TW) is someone who creates, structures, and publishes relevant information for a target audience in a timely manner. A TW generally works in a specific industry sector, creating modular content to describe complex products or processes. Their role is to bridge the information gap between product developer and end-user, juggling a diverse set of tools for communication, project management, content design, and publishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best practices for developer documentation</title>
      <link>http://example.org/best-practice-for-tech-docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/best-practice-for-tech-docs/</guid>
      <description>Structure your documentation It is important to structure your content in an easy-to-navigate manner.
Navigation structure To develop a clear visual hierarchy on your documentation website:
 Organise menus by topic Group similar types of content under the same menu Use a maximum of two levels of submenu  Make the documentation searchable Documentation must be searchable and information easy to find. Some recommendations include:
 Create short, unique, and accurate page titles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/readme/</guid>
      <description>technical-writing These sample pieces of writing are deliberately generic; they do not reference any proprietary technology or software which would be subject to a NDA entered into by me in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
